A Guide to the Harry W. Frantz photographs FA097
Rockefeller Archive Center
Harry W. Frantz photographs
1942-1945
Rockefeller Archive Center
United States. Office of the Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs
Frantz, Harry W.
FA097
0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists entirely of photographs.
San Francisco (Calif.); Photographs
- Harry W. Frantz, 1942-1945; 1051; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
  - News Photos and Memoribilia of the Argentine Journalists Tour of U. S. A., 1943 (Box 39, Folder 384)
    Scope and Contents note
    Group photos, Journalists, Argentina, WWII
  - Press Personal File of H. W. F.; Articles, Photos and Memoribilia, undated (Box 39, Folder 385)
    Journalists, Mexico, Office workers
  - Tour of Argentine Journalists in the United States and Canada, 1943, Vol. 1 (Box 39, Folder 386)
    Journalists, Argentina, Group portraits, WWII,
  - Tour of Argentine Journalists in the United States and Canada March-April Vol II, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 387)
    Argentina, Journalists, Conferences
  - Content and Directives, Special Assignments, Addresses and Expositions, undated (Box 40, Folder 388)
    Travel
  - Letters and Articles about H. W. F. Trips, 1942-1944 (Box 40, Folder 389)
    Mexico, Travel
  - Catch-all Volume of Surplus Publications, Photos and News, undated (Box 40, Folder 390)
    Travel, Group portraits
  - Chapultepec Conference, Mexico City, Feb-March 1945, Vol II (Box 40, Folder 391)
    Conferences, Mexico
  - Photo Newspictures of San Francisco and Environs and the UN meeting, undated (Box 40, Folder 392)
    UN Conferences, California landscape, Cities